Jon Dyson

Full Stack Developer

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self motivated and adaptive full stack developer, with several years of experience in small team project oriented environments. Previously founded a technology driven startup, which included direct development work as well as the management of contracted development. Possesses a strong background in financial risk assessment and financial feasibility studies.

EXPERIENCE

Lotus Import Group – Founder (Full Stack Dev), 2014 – 16

Created a portfolio of ecommerce websites focused on the manufacture, importation, and direct sales of a variety of consumer goods.

US Army - Civil Affairs Operator, 2008 - 16

Civil Affairs Operators deploy in small teams and function autonomously to develop and implement small to large scale cultural and economic projects and programs. Planning often begins and ends with a detailed financial feasibility study.

International Financial Group - Underwriting, 2011-14

Responsible for providing both a business risk, and financial risk assessment of commercial general liability in the high risk excess and surplus lines market. Policy risk exposure ranged from 2M to 10M aggregate.

EDUCATION

RefactorU, CO— Full Stack Immersion Course, 2016

Graduated from the RefactorU immersion learning program focused on MEAN stack development.

UConn, CT— Bachelor's Degree (BGS), 2010

Graduated with a concentration in Sociology and a minor in economics from The University of Connecticut.

Special Operations Center of Excellence, NC - CivilAffairs Operator, 2008

Graduated from the US Army's Special Warfare Center & School in the top 5% of the class (Commandant's List)







JonDyson.com

hello@jondyson.com linkedin.com/in/jon-dyson github.com/DysonJ 860.309.5343

SKILLS

Technical

Javascript

Angular

Node.js

Express.js

MongoDB

Git

jQuery

CSS

Materialize

Bootstrap Stylus

mySQL

msAccess

HTML

ColdFusion

Professional Development

Toastmasters: 1 Year



AWARDS

Army Commendation Medal

Awarded for rapid assimilation and cultural understanding in an austere environment.

Commandant's List

Graduated from the Army's Special Warfare Center in the top 5% of the class.



refactor

CLEARANCE

DoD Security Clearance:



Combat Veteran Operation **Enduring Freedom**



